Trung Long Le

Front-end Developer



Hi, I'm Long, I'm front-end developer with 2 year with React (1+ YOE with typescript), over 6 months with React-native. Beside that I had experience with NodeJs and symfony. Have strong in independent work skill and problem solving

Ho Chi Minh

Work Experience

Front-end Developer

02/2021 - 02/2022

CTA Solution

Build an web application for manage order and workflows of department
Build an OKRs web application for manage and improve work performance
Build an Finance web application for manage debt, cash flow
Build landing page for marketing in some feature events of the year
(summer vacation, mid autumn,..)

Responsibility:

- · Development frontend site
- Testing
- Maintenance

Language programming: HTML,CSS, JS , JQuery ReactJs (Redux-saga, Pusher(BEAMS)), Symfony

Mobile Developer

VSPORT

02/2022 - 09/2022

Build production social network app

Responsibility:

- · Build component core
- Maintenance

Language programming: React native, Nextjs, socket

Front-end Developer

TavicoSoft

10/2022 - Present

Build Web application for manage workflows Build Web application for manage documents Responsibility:

- · Build component core, custom library
- Maintenance
- Testing

Language programming: ReactJs, socket, firebase, jquery, bpmn

Education

Bachelor, Software Technology

09/2017 - 06/2022 Grad

Thu Dau Mot University

Graduated with GPA 7.0 and English EPT certificate 7.1